It's finally begun.   For
the past several hundred years, there has always been a match before me
.   The
black king remained seated as
before, conveying an air of composure, of arrogance.  I have never
forgotten those eyes in these 500 years of music.  When the curse of the sect was cast, there was no trace of pity in the eyes of death's loss.   A
traveler who carried waves and traversed six countries before arriving in this land.  That thing now
seeks a meeting with our God.  Is it for the sake of sincere
dialogue, or is there another motive?  By
gathering the hearts of other gods, you can break through the limits of your abilities as the Ice [Music] Demon
.
By gathering the bones of the Third Advent, we may be able to
witness the legacy he sealed away.   They say that if we
gather this holy committee, we might be able to defy death
.  Ah, I'm sure that in the past, she made a
pact with her ancestors and bestowed upon her power, hoping for this very thing
.
That's it.  I'm not going to run away.   It's
not over yet.   I do
n't sing just for myself.   This is also for
all the water creatures that have sung here
.  I'm the only one here right now.   I'm the only one who can
protect this singing voice [music]
.   It's
time to go on stage.  [Music] Is
this a turn for those who have returned to find out?  Our love is truly wounded by Tenri.
[Music] That's
strange.  Why do I sense Pavlina's presence from you? Ah, so I failed after all.
[Music] If
everyone agrees to break the seal, the
true layer from 500 [Music] years ago will also be revealed.
[Music] I haven't been
attached to the fragments of sword ability that have been taken from me until now.  However, resisting the refinement of life force with that power is an
unforgivable battle.   Now I can finally
bring death to my heart's content.  For a very long time now, Sunezina has been a country that could be destroyed at any moment by the Nail of Judgment.
[Music]
[Music] Have
you ever met tomorrow?
[Music] The
shadow of the sacred spacetime of death and Tenri exists everywhere, and civilization is not a lie given by fate.
[Music] Do you
seriously think you can stand up to me head-on?
enjoy putting on a show of godlike determination?  I won't mention any significant price or suffering.  Robber.  Let's move on to the next plan.
[Music] It seems there's
something that needs to be reclaimed.  Are you trying to stop me?  Ice Genie.
[Music]
ສ
[Music] Good evening
, travelers.  There are many children like that
.  Yes, I'm happy to see you all again
.  I think this was about two years
ago, wasn't it?  I fondly remember the time we spoke here
.  yes.  So, I look forward to working with you again this time
.  yes
.  So, this time we have a
new member joining us from Snezhnaya
.  Now, please introduce yourself.   Hello
everyone, Paimon Paimon, good evening
.
Good evening, this is Uesaka Shimire, playing the role of Arai.  This is my first reservation.  I wish you the best.  Huh? Oh, was that Ode-san just now?
[laughs]
No, no, I don't think so.  I think I was wrong.
No, that doesn't seem to be the case.
Wait, wait, no way.
Huh? I can't do it, I can't do it anymore.  Huh,
[laugh]
remember?
Remember.   That
's Odette.  Odette.  Yeah.  Well, um, please take care of me.
[Laughs]
Yes, thank you very much.
yay.  happy.
thank you.
yes.  It's Uesaka-san.   It's
Uesaka-san.  please.
[Laughs]
Please.  [Shouting]
Yes.
Okay.  Let me go.
[Laughs] Let's get this party started!   It was
incredibly quiet during Odette's performance.   That's right
.   I've been speaking in the
quietest voice I've ever spoken in the last 15 years, so today, uh, is it okay if I speak loudly?
[laughs] Sure
, go ahead.
Ah, let me out.  Bye-bye
[laugh]
Nice to meet you.   thank you
.
[Laughs]
Help me.
[Screaming]
Scary, scary, scary, scary.   I did it
.  It's a gun.
[Shouting] Oh,
amazing.
Wow, today is amazing!  What are you going to do?
Today is today, yes.  It's a preview program
[laughs] A
preview program.  [Laughs]
Yes.
yes.  This is a preview program for the original version
7.1, Requiem to the Underworld
.
Yes
.  Well, I'd say the temperature difference is a bit too extreme.  Oh, it's right at the start of the season.   I
think everyone has seen the PV, which is packed with a lot of information, and with
this scene in particular, it might be difficult to process.
yes.  Sneage seemed to be in imminent danger.
yes.   I'm looking forward to seeing what kind of
story unfolds in the new version.   I'm looking forward to it
.
What's the version name? This "M" for Meisei looks
cool.   That's
cool.  Yeah.  [Music] I have a
feeling something really big is about to happen.
[Clears throat]
Indeed, there is a requiem and the underworld, but nothing else.   This probably is
n't a regular meeting.   It doesn't seem like a
regular gathering.  That's certainly true.
[Laughs] It was like a
huge pounding beat.
yes.
yes.  The fact that it's a Lecture M suggests a newlywed feel.
Yeah.  yes.  That's correct.   It's a
song that soothes the soul.  Yeah.
Sneezing, you know, when it comes to
songs, yes
.   Doesn't that
remind you of Heli Madonna?
Yes.  It's because of that water that the beautiful song wasn't recited.
Oh, oh my
,
oh my.  To spread rumors.  Oh dear.  scared.  Oh.  Yeah.  Yeah.  My throat is in perfect condition.  Hello.  I'm a loser.  It's because of the water.
[Scream]
[Snort]
But that doesn't matter.
I'm the best singer in the Korolevsky Theatre Company.  That's all you need to remember.  Hello everyone.  I'm Itooka, playing the role of Prima Donna Bocha in the Koloreski Troupe at Sneage's House.  Leliver
[laugh]
What happened? It's cha.   A lot of
amazing things were happening before Chan arrived, was
n't it like the climax? It was just now, nothing.
[Laughs]
Not at all.  Is something wrong? Nothing at all
.  Was this how Odeto was? Never mind.
[Laughs]
[Laughs] Was that so?
But I feel like that was the case with Jats.  Yes, I think that was the
relationship.  [Laughs]
Huh? Huh? We're good friends.
yes.  It's because they're good friends, right?   That's right
.   He's very assertive, though
.
Podette is sniffing.
[Laughs]
But I think I just heard a really loud voice a moment ago, or was that just a hallucination?
Ah, well, you know.
Yeah.   Ah
, that feels so refreshing.  [Laughs]
That's good to hear.   By
the way, this is my first time appearing on a preview program.
thank you.   I'm
really looking forward to it.
What are we going to do? What are we going to do?
What are we going to do? What are we going to do? I hear we'll be talking a lot about the story and characters of Sneezia, right? Looking forward to it
.
fun.  welcome.  welcome.  Okay, so today's preview program will be
presented by these three people.   thank you
.   They're
so energetic.  They're so energetic.  [Laughs] A
theater with a waiting room system.   I don't
think they were that kind of people.  amazing.
[Laughs]
That's right.  It's the Colore Theater Company.  It's like this.   I see
.  That's important, isn't it?
Really [laughs] So, without
further ado
, in version 7.0
, we uncovered the conspiracy of the deadly lost Ronova in the theater.
[Music]
Yeah.   And
, furthermore, we discussed the mistletoe plan that Snezhnaya is pursuing in order to resist Tenri, right?
[Music]
Yes.   That's what happened
.
Yeah.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.   The
crisis within Sneage is far from over, and the donkey is not about to back down.
Carelessness is the worst thing you can do.
Well,
as you can see from the previous version PV, the situation inside Sneiji is now critical and there is no time to lose.
Wow.  What will happen to the characters that you've just met?
Yeah.  But at
the end of version 7.0, Suna's female companion returned from her expedition, right?   welcome back
.   Welcome back
.  I'm sure there's something they've created.
Yeah.
That is it.
yes.  In version 7.0, the
female character finally appeared towards the end of the Demon Lord mission.
Oh, it's savings, oh, the head maid Danica
and Commander Vesna of Dorzina also made an appearance.
Yeah.
yes.   I have a
feeling that I'll finally be able to have a proper conversation with Onnagyo during the next demon mission.  But how can I meet the woman and see her?
Ah,
first we could meet Danica and Besna, who are being used as prostitutes.
[music]
Ah, that's true.
Vesna, who appeared alongside the Queen, gave off a surprisingly approachable impression for a commander, didn't she?  Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.
Yes, you
can meet Vesna again in version 7.1.
Yeah.  Well, apparently that encounter happens quite suddenly.   Huh?  The
traveler encounters someone at the Cellar Garden Restaurant, and soon after, he comes face to face with Besna, but even then, he somehow senses an enemy in her.   Even
seasoned travelers seem to be drawn to this charming atmosphere.
No, I like maids with mean-looking eyes.
[Laughs] I could
watch this forever.  I hope they keep having enemies forever.
[Laughs]
Yes.  Well, their attitude towards travelers seems completely different, but I wonder what they're talking about.  yes.
Well, I suppose it's a brief greeting before formally meeting the woman.
Oh, hmm, hmm.
Yeah.  Yeah.
Well, Sneji should be fairly wary of travelers.  Really.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.
But finally, we get to meet Sneage's woman, which is very thought-provoking,
[music] and I'm sure
all of you travelers have a lot of questions after this long journey, so I hope that at least some of those questions will be answered.  Yeah.  Yeah.   They
gather the will of God and rebel against the principles of heaven.  The woman has quite an ambitious plan.  yes.
Yeah.
Regarding that, well, in the story that follows, you will learn the true purpose behind the Queen collecting the hearts of the gods.   It's finally happening
.
[shouting] Yeah
yes.   I had
heard since my travels that Sneiji's women were gathering the hearts of the gods, but now I finally understand
why.   That's right
.
yes.
Okay, let me introduce them briefly.
Please be aware that there will be quite a few spoilers from here on out.
Spoiler alert, spoiler alert,
spoiler alert.   It's
dangerous.  Attention.   be careful
.   It starts from
here.   I'm going
.
yes.   According to
Onnagyo, it seems that by borrowing the power of the hearts of the gods that she has gathered, she can amplify her own power and gain the strength to resist the laws of heaven.
[Music]
Yeah.   And the
heart of God is
said to be the bones of the Third Coming.
[Music]
So, in
other words, the female practitioners are trying to oppose Tenri by using forces from outside the world.
[Music]
Yeah.  That's amazing.
yes.  This is getting into a big topic about skeletons.
Yeah.  Even
things that are impossible with the power of one God's heart might become
possible if we combine seven of them, right?
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.
Well, that's not all.
[Music] And
now, the woman reveals another reason why she attracts the hearts of the gods to travelers
.  What is this place in Sneige's Yapalace?  yes.  This is also new information.  Yeah.
[Music]
Yeah.  I'm going.
Yes, this is the
seal left behind by the Third Coming, known only to women and a very select few.
law.
yes.  Actually, this seal only reacts to the heart of a god.
Wow.
So, if we gather all of God's hearts, we'll find a way to break the seal?
Uh,
yes.
yes.   oh.
[Laughs] That was
quick.   You
know everything, don't you?   be
familiar with.  Wow, that's
amazing!  That's amazing.   This
is the script.
[Laughs]
Yes.  Well, right now, rather than searching for the heart of the last engine, it's more important to resolve the crisis that's threatening Snage.
yes.  yes.   It's
a script, but it's really [laughing] It's a
script, they say.   It's all according to
the script.  [Laughs] This is the
main street.   I agree
.
Oh, so the crisis looming over Sneage's house is the
death of Ronova, right?   Sigh
.  Well, in the version 7.0
demon mission, I learned firsthand the importance of taking measures to prevent technological advancement within Sneage.  Well, it was really
annoying.  [Laughs]
Seriously, what is this?
Us, us.
See,
victim, victim.  [Laughs]
Yes, yes, yes.  That's a problem, isn't it?
But with such
powerful measures,
technology is no longer advancing.
hey.   And so
, Snejina was forced to suspend the Mistletoe Project, which she had been working on to resist Tenri.
[Music]
Yes.
yes.
But Sunezina cannot give up the research she is conducting to resist the laws of nature, in order to avoid becoming a repeat of Karya and for the sake of her ideals as a woman.
Yeah.
yes.  For Sneage, Ronova, who wields the power of death, is now... well
.  This is the biggest obstacle.
Well, I've mentioned Kinki, the island in the sky, so many times now
[music] I'm sure there are
many travelers who are worried that the situation is getting quite dangerous, and that's exactly right
.   It was really strange
.  [Laughs]
Right [gasps]
.  For Sneiji, who wants to put his plan into action, the top priority is to sever ties and somehow resolve the situation in Rono.
Yeah.  Yeah.
yes.
So, in order to protect both the travelers and the pies, he readily agreed to participate in the plan.
[Music]
Thanks for the cool trip.  Protect Paimon.
Paimon is the best friend, after all.   That's right
.   You
absolutely must not let Nova take you there.
No.
yes.  Oh, by the way
[laughs]
Yes.
This new plan is a major one that will involve the entire nation in joining Sneage.
yes.
Yeah.   That's how it is for
travelers.  The traveler will carry out this plan together with Phi's sense of execution and, well, with his comrades within Sneage.   It really is a temporary arrangement
.
yes.  Oh, it seems Besna will also lend us the power of the wind, passed down through the Villa clan, to help the plan proceed smoothly.
[Music]
Furthermore,
in the story, you will encounter a mysterious person who knows a lot about it.
[Music]
Who could it be?
Uh, you don't really know much about Kaloya, do you?
Yeah.
Who? Who?
Who? [laughs]
Yes.  Well, this time everyone in Sneage will be working together, but of course, that means we'll also be working together with the Fatui.  Ah, well
, anyway, Sneijuna is going to clash head-on with the deadly blunder.
Yeah.
Ah!   Yes
.  Wow [laughs]
Yes.  Ah, well, this time, within Sneage, we will truly rebel against the death that carries out the will of Tenri.
[Music]
Well, the discrepancies are also in the script, but,
uh, what? what? what? what? It might end up causing a
big problem in the end.  It's amazing how many dots there are.   An
ominous X mark,
what's the X mark? An
X mark from Tenri,
we're being kicked again
[laugh] I don't like it
.   I don't want to
go back to square one or have my
raw gems taken away
.  It's a big place where anything can happen
.
Well, even
now it's a pretty bad punishment, but that was a pretty big one, wasn't it?  Aren't we supposed to be "bad"?   I got
caught up in it.   I got
caught up in it.
Yes, well, it was an accident, a self-inflicted accident,
[laugh] but I wonder if it's
okay to just categorize it as an accident
.
yes.   Speaking of
death and loss, in version
7.0 [Music] they try to
retrieve Baimon right in front of the traveler, and it's a
retrieval, after all.  I think it's a monster.  No, that's not it.
yes.  It was as if they didn't care about the travelers at all.   I ca
n't forgive Baemon.   It's
not a secret.   That's right
.   That's
unfair.  That's unreasonable.  It's Mashiko.  mascot.  Masco.  trout.
[Laughs]
Good kid.  [Laughs] What a good
kid.
Uh, her sword technique is Shimo
. Yes.   That's
incredibly unfair, isn't it?
yes.
Nobody realized that she was already dead even before the fight with her began.  That's scary, isn't it?   I was like, "Ugh."
Yeah.
Now, tell me.   How
many times do you want to experience it before it's too late? It's too late to
regret it now.  Let me receive the blow of death upon myself.  As expected of the
Four Shadows.
Yeah.
yes.  It's incredibly intimidating.
Yeah.   Can we
win? Can we win? What will happen? What do we have to do to win? It seems even more amazing
than when it was version 7.0
.   Are you sure you'll be
alright facing such a formidable enemy?
[Music] Well
, you were manipulating the enemy as if they were toys.
yes.   The
power of death is truly overwhelming.
yes.   When you
fight her, make sure to avoid her area-of-effect attacks, and also be
careful of the Death Sword ability that Ronova uses.
Wow, that's tough.
Yeah.
Oh, be careful.  You'll get caught.
[Scream]
Ah, ah, that was
close.   Run away
.
[Laughs]
And here comes a big
[shout] Come
quickly.
Faster.  [Laughs] You should have come
sooner.  thank you.
thank you.   In the
song of the moon, when we hunted and defeated the moon, he came to our aid.
yes.  Thank you again for helping us this time.  thank you.  I'll come sooner,
[laughs]
if possible, when it's on Peach.
[Music]
Please.  yes.  But, if we have Dai Thrive there, then yes
.   I think the approval rating
for Ronoronoronoba will increase from now on.   I see
.
Yeah.
Yeah.  Yeah.  In version 7.0
, the Death Stance was practically an unbeatable force, so I'm sure
all the travelers are wondering how we'll end up fighting it.
Yeah, that's true.  The battle against the loss of love will be extremely tough for everyone involved.
Yeah.
Moreover, that's not the only
enemy.   oh.
Oh,
as you saw in the PV earlier, the music by Sei no
Shissei Raindot also makes an appearance.
[clears throat]
Ah, the
encounter between her and the woman was quite tense.
[Music]
Yeah.
Wait, as if a death-related mistake wasn't enough, now a se-related mistake is coming too? Is it going to get involved? It is.   I ca
n't believe I was reading about the loss of true life.  There's no way you'll lose your life
[laugh] It's
death.  [Laughs] It's
not about life and death.
[Laughs] I
thought she was a fresh, fresh person,
but
what exactly is she up to? Is she going to punish her too?
Oh, is she going to be punished too? What do you think?
Yeah.  Looks strong.
Wait, I never imagined that the
loss of those two would manifest itself in such a way.
Wait, what's going to happen to Sneiji next? What's going to happen? For the exciting developments, please see for yourselves, travelers!   They wo
n't tell you this.  Oh, that's interesting.  From here
[laugh]
Yes.  Also, if you complete the Demon Lord mission in version [Music]
7.1, you will
not only receive 620 raw gems, but you will also
get character ascension materials for two new characters, Les and Bojanitz.  I did it.   I did it
.
yes.  Well, in Snezhnaya this time, you can experience various stories in addition to the story of the demon lord mission.
Yeah.
Well, due to certain circumstances, the woman bestowed a special status upon the traveler, giving him the opportunity to be involved in various matters concerning Sneiji.
yes.   Starting
with version 7.1, travelers will be able to receive special orders from the Secretary's Office.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.   If you
complete the mission, you will not only be able to help the women deal with various matters within Sneji, but you will also gain a
deeper understanding of the current situation within Sneji.
Ah, it seems we might also learn about the political ideals of the female emperor.
Yeah.
yes.  Since various races live in Sunezina and the Great, even the women cannot fully grasp everything within Sunezina.
Yeah.  Yeah.
For example, it seems she wants to know how the people within the country view her from a different perspective.
Yeah.  Yeah.   In
this version, the traveler will gather the thoughts of their close companions and the common people, and depict the image of the woman that resides in each of their hearts.  Yeah.
Yeah.
yes.  Yeah.   And, you can have a
casual chat with the Sneage staff, and you can also get a glimpse of the bonds between the comrades.   Oh really?   It seems some
familiar faces have also come to visit.
Oh, by all means, please do talk to them and ask how they've been doing lately.
For example, there's the
Funtenu Table Talk Theater Accompanying Group.
Oh,
apparently they're holding an event in Sneezia.
Yes, it looks fun.
yes.  yes.  And, Vesna, the commander of the Empress's troops, Druzina, also goes out
into town herself to conduct fraud prevention campaigns.   It looks like
something a local government would do.
[Laughs]
Yes.
So, they are actively and wholeheartedly fulfilling their responsibility to protect the safety of the people.
thank you.
Oh, that reminds me, I heard that Besna received training from Faday in terms of execution and physical fitness.
Yeah.   It's not just about
guidance.
Huh?
Danica and Besna have been learning various techniques from their captain since they were little.
Oh, really?  The captain is the mentor of both of them.
Yeah.
Yeah.  If you've been trained by that captain since you were little, then
yes.  It's no wonder those two have
risen to their current positions.
Yeah.
Moreover, Vesna was the youngest commander to achieve victory
.  amazing.
Yeah.  Yeah.
Moreover, simply having ability isn't enough to become a commander.   He
swears absolute neutrality to women, and is capable of handling various gyms within the sneakers for the sake of women.  That's why Besna was chosen.  Ah, she looks very approachable, but she is, after all, the head of the women's personal unit.  yes.  Don't underestimate it.  yes.   That's right
.  They might be able to uncover everything about you just by talking to you for a short while.
[Music]
Today, let's
delve deeper into Besna through this video.  please.  Putting all the vegetables you dislike on the same plate is a bit rude.  Fluffy.  Sigh.   It's
not over yet.  Let me explain the whole story from the bottom of my heart.
That's it.  I won't let you get away.  Let's go.  They fight with incredible agility.
Yeah.   A
small, sword-like object was attacking alongside it.
Huh, what is that?
What could that be? Is it
? [laughs]
What is that? Please tell me.   That's
something I'll leave to your imagination.
[Laughs] I
thought it was very good from my mouth,
[Laughs] but I
thought it was a sword.  I wonder what it is
.  So,
[laughs] it's a
magical weapon that Resna created by fusing her own consciousness with elemental energy
.   Then you ca
n't call it a sword.
Well, if you think it's a sword, then it's a sword.
[Laughs] So you're saying I can think whatever I want
?
If you think this is a sword, then it's a sword.   I
thought it was a sword.  That's something sharp.  It's starting to look like that.  Yes, Busna can use the power of Anemo stars to transform Cryo Diffusion reactions into Star Diffusion reactions, increasing the Star Diffusion damage for the entire team.
[Laughs]
Oh.
Ah, Hoshikasan,
yes.   I believe it was
introduced in version 7.0, right?
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.  Hmph.  Yeah.   I imagine
many travelers are already using it in this way, but could you please introduce it again? Yes.  First, when a diffusion reaction occurs, it explodes over time, generating something called a star storm that deals targeted damage.
[Laughs]
Yeah.  Yeah.   The
idea is that if you cause more star dispersion before the explosion, the starstorm will be strengthened and be able to inflict greater damage.
By the way, if you get
hit by a Starstorm explosion, you can fly higher, which is
useful for exploration and travel.   Oh really?   It's
useful for getting around.   I see.
So, it's not just a new combat system, then?   It's
not like someone who listens to the textbook and then asks the professor [laughs].   No, there isn't
.
Oh, are there any other new elements that are unique to Sneage?
Yes.  Huh, by doing the Star Reversal [laughs], we
can now also interfere with the goats' actions and create areas to escape the cold.
Yes, with the arrival of Vesna, it seems there will be even more opportunities for stellar diffusion reactions to play a role.
[Laughs]
That's right.  Besina acquires the sword by activating her current skill, etc.
By consuming this, you can unleash special elemental skills, but if there is a starstorm nearby, some of the damage will be treated as star-diffusion reaction damage.
Hmm.
Wow, you have a really diverse range of fighting styles.
Yeah.   It seems like they have
some kind of particular preference or preference.   That's right
.   I think I remember
.  That's the trick.  When they talked about the damage to Chonoko, the professor was like, "Oh, I didn't know that existed," and kind of left the room.  I got out.  Everyone's left.  Right now, Doctor
[laugh]
[laugh] it's
amazing.  Oh,
what do you think? It looks like it might happen.  I'm not a doctor.  So, Besna's fighting style is inherited from the ancient Wind Spirits, the successors of the historic Wind Spirits clan, the Striboja, right?   On
the other hand, you can't recover energy with normal attacks after activating Elemental Skeleton, and
since it consumes swords, special elemental skills are progressively strengthened to deal higher damage.  Yeah.
[Music] Oh,
really?  Combined with their light and nimble movements, it's truly a pleasure to watch.   The
professor is a little tired.  The professor was gone.
[Laughs] I've come
back to this voice today.  Please tell me the long one.
[Laughs]
Huh, not even more?  Oh, so if she activates her elemental burst, Resna can recover a certain amount of research and deal area damage to enemies?
Yes, [shouts] the
way he launches attacks that send out such a high-pitched scream is truly befitting of a commander.   That's right
.  Actually, Besna likes to collect various items that make her happy, such as jewelry.
[Laughs]
Yeah.  nice.  Yeah.  Yeah.   As soon as she gets into something, she tries to get her hands on it, so
Besna herself, who collects such things, has become synonymous with a glamorous and dazzling presence.
[Music] I see
.
Vesna himself said this.
Oh, well, how do I even put that into words?
Yeah.  Well, I'll just speculate.
[Laughs] That's just
speculation.   Let's
remember.  No way, that's impossible.
[Laughs] If you
miss that fleeting moment of excitement, the joy you feel when you get it later will be halved.  So, you should get what you want now.
[Music]
and [Laughter] have
returned.  The professor is amazing.
[Laughs]
The doctor is amazing.  What the doctor heard.   That's
amazing.  It can also become that.   I can't wait to hear it
.  Please share your thoughts.  [Laughs]
Well, what's more, the Vesna can also fly at high speeds in non-combat situations.
Wow, that's amazing.
amazing.   She
switches to Vesna in mid-air and then flies away.  That's amazing.   So, it seems that the
wind really does make it possible to fly.
Wow.
Oh, well, there are other interesting stories about Besna.
Oh, that sounds interesting.   It's
long.  I still want to know more.  I want to know.  tell me.
[Laughs]
Oh, well then, I'll give a battle touch to a different teacher.  Please switch to a different teacher.
Oh, it's the teacher.   fault
.  Ah, well, one day Besna accidentally found a
secret book that described a healthy training method, and when she tried
infusing her sword with spiritual power as instructed in the book, it
miraculously transformed into a wise and powerful being and ran away
.  Wow
, [laughing] I can't get any color information in
.  Teacher,
teacher, wait a minute, wow
, the road to 1000 people is to run away.
[Laughs] Well,
yeah.  So where are those spirits? What happened to them?
What happened to them? Do you
want to know?
Yes.   I
want to know.  [Shouting] It ca
n't be helped, die.
[Laughs] A
haphazard,
sloppy kind of sexiness.
[Laughs]
Yeah.  It's not quite the third character, though.   It looks like they
caused a minor problem.   Some
spirits are obsessed with war medicine, while others are diligently training.  Furthermore, some of them secretly collect various gemstones, so it seems like
each of them has their own special talents.
[Breathtaking sound]
So the traveler was asked by Besna to help bring these spirits back.   Oh really?  They're all so
unique.
Yeah.  Yeah.   I'm looking forward to seeing how things
unfold.
Yes.  After resolving the troubles caused by the spirits
[laugh], the
traveler acquires a unique, believable, imaginative appearance, like that sign, that crunchy thing that can be made.   The
crunchy kind.  [Laughs] The
crunchy kind.   You know, that thing that makes a
crackling sound that you sometimes press by mistake
.  It acquires the appearance of,
uh, the connecting device you see when exploring the world
.  Yeah.
You know, the one that's convenient for getting around.
[Laughs]
Yeah.  I've never really called him by his name before, but that's his.  Oh, so, it seems you'll be able to change the appearance.
Oh, so we can get the right to have Besna herself provide the sound again?   Oh really?   When
Besna flies through the sky, Rei comes along with her.  That's nice.   It has a
special feel to it, doesn't it?
Oh, and it seems Besna has even more hobbies.  My
hobby.  Yeah.
Oh, I
feel like I saw Besna quite often in the theater during version 7.0.  Could it be that it's completely intense?
Hmm.  That's absolutely correct.
[Laughs] I did it
.   You must be very
busy.   They've gone out of their way to take time off work to come and see the show
at the theater.
Our Kolofsky Theatre Company has many fans, you know.
[Music]
Suddenly, suddenly.  Huh? Huh? [laughs]
Huh? Where's the teacher? Where was the teacher?
Teacher.
Who are you talking about? Oh, did I keep it a secret? Podette's back.   I'm back
.  Welcome back.  is.  [Laughs]
Podette, how long has it been?   It seems
a little suspicious.  It seems suspicious, and they might be back.
[Laughs] Welcome back
.   Welcome back
.
yes.  Well, it makes sense, considering even the bailiffs in Fadi are attending his lectures.
Yeah.
yes.
Oh, right, that's right.  Speaking of the Korolevsky Theatre Company, in version
7.0 there's the ballet scene in Odette, and
yeah.   There was a
song by Posini-chan, you know
.  It was definitely really good, wasn't it?
[Music]
Yeah.
Bojanits is the Puli Madonna of the theater troupe, you know.
Pulley Madonna.  [Laughs] That's
right.   My
mother, Jinny, sings a lot, not only on stage but also in her daily life.   I sometimes
sing lullabies to her puppies, and it's nice.   They
all fall asleep after I sing just a little bit.
Lonely [laughs] The
moon is feeling a little lonely.  She falls asleep so quickly, she's such a
caring child.
yes.
Yeah.  They also encourage me to get plenty of rest, which is
really nice.  No.   That's right
.  She's a really good girl.
[Laughs] She's
such a good kid, isn't she?   That's right
.
thank you.
Thank you so much.  Thank you for being born.
[Laughs]
Thank you.
Also, my older brother really loves to do ass-shaking with everyone.
Yeah.   Do you remember me complaining about how
poorly Chegunov treated his staff during negotiations?
Yes.   I've
lived in Sneznea my whole life, so I care about the people.
Yeah.  Yeah.
That's why I'm participating in Rocot.   I want to do
something for the people who are being treated unfairly because of the illusory statistics.
kind.   That's right
.   She's a
really good girl.  She's a really good girl.
yes.
In the version 7.0 storyline, she helped everyone with her singing voice.  And she also showed us the mysterious power of her singing voice, which is influenced by water.
yes.  The singing voice of Mizu no Sei is not just beautiful.
Yeah.
And actually, Bojini
has another form, have you noticed? Oh, excuse me, are you perhaps talking about Re? I feel like I might have seen something like that when I accidentally walked into Bojinii's singing practice room
.
yes.   The
fact that you have fins on both your legs means you must have lost something in exchange for them,
right?
Yes, yes, yes,
actually,
actually [scream] it's
nothing.   I don't have any
.  What is this conversation? [laughs]
Yes.  That's not the case at all.  What's this about?
Normally, they have legs so they can easily walk on land and in the air, but when they return to the water, they swim around in their original form.   It's actually
easier to swim when you swim in your original form.   That's right
.  I can swim fast, too.
Yeah.   On my
days off, I sometimes swim to other countries.
Wow, that's amazing.  [Laughs] Yes,
there is.   They'll just
swim away.
Incidentally, for some reason, I think Fontaine water suits my skin particularly well.   It must
suit your skin.  I wonder if it feels good? Certainly, the temperature and the feel of the water on the skin.
Things like what kind of water there is
[laughs] like it's moist
.  Something like a water-based perfume from a country of water, perhaps?  surely.  Well, it's good.  Delicious water.   It's
delicious.  The water there is delicious.   Maybe I can
drink the water
.  Indeed, since it's all about the water, I'm quite particular about it.  Yeah.
And that's also the
origin of mermaid legends found in other countries.  Boji: That's right
.
Besides that, it can freely transform into a water-based form and act accordingly.  Yeah.   The fins
sparkle beautifully in the sunlight.
yes.   Also,
during battles, she transforms into a water-elemental form and uses the water element's divine eye to support her team members with her singing voice.  Oh, so they
fight while singing.   oh.
yes.   I'd like to
show you all a little bit of it.
[snorts]
Now, please enjoy the special lecture by Bo Jini.
[Music][Singing]
Look, look, my tail is turning into a tail.  Let's all
sing music!   oh.   It was a completely new
fighting style that incorporated singing.  yes.  This is how Bojanitsa fights.
When she activates her elemental skill, she reveals her true form as a water elemental and heals damaged team members on the field with her singing.
[Music]
Yeah.   It
also reduces the enemy's Hydro and Cryo elemental resistance and increases the upper character's bullet resistance.
Yeah.  Furthermore, while the skill is active, it
increases the amount of Density and Ice elemental damage dealt by all team members, based on your own maximum HP.
[Music] This is a huge
help.
yes.  So, it not only heals you, but also strengthens you, right?
Yeah.  Yeah.  It seems like it would be very useful in formations that utilize freezing reactions.
yes.  Will you be very active? Yes.
[Laughs] There's still more!  The
nature of the star storm actually changes depending on the influence of the singing voice.   In
addition to its original effect, it can also lower the enemy's wind element stance and further increase waist reaction damage.  Yeah.   So, that means you can not
only support the freeze reaction but also
strengthen the stellar diffusion reaction team?
Yes.  yes.  That's right.
Yeah.   This
child is very versatile.
Yeah.  [Laughs]
Hey.
Yes, during her elemental burst, Bojanitsa sings a song about water, and her voice resonates around her, dealing area-of-effect water damage.   oh.
Well, if my big brother is there, the possibilities for our fighting styles will probably expand considerably.   Let's
spread the word.  If only Saishuu was there
[laughs] I do
n't want to fight anymore without my big brother.
[Laughs] We can't do without him
.  No.
[Laughs]
Yes.  And as for that big brother, it was mentioned before that the production costs for the original team were
discussed in the context of the production philosophy of Sneage and the future.
yes.   I'm sure many of you who
watched that video were interested in traveling.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Yeah.   So, I'd like you to take a good
listen to Posini's singing voice.
[Music]
Wow.
Hmm.
amazing.  [Shouting] They'll
even sing Akapera while playing instruments
.  yes.   It's clear that the
Johnny's boys really love to sing.   That's right
.   The
song is yeah.   It's a
way to express your true feelings, and also a way to connect with others.
Yeah.  Yeah.  That's why, unlike Odette, he's kind to his fans.
No, no, Detto has its own merits, you know.   Let's do it
.  [Laughs]
Well, that's true.  That's what's good about it
.   I get the
impression that he really cherishes the people who come to listen to his songs.   That's right
.  Bojanitsa genuinely loves singing.  Yeah.   I even prepare
gifts for people who come to listen to my songs seriously.
[Shouting]
Yes.
For example, at the disguise bureau of the Bojanitour mission, they give travelers a special notebook so they can write down important plans.
Yeah.   And you might even
receive an even more special gift.  It must be a different present.
Please enjoy the game for more details.
yes.  So, will we learn a lot about Bojiniza during the mission? Yes.   During the
mission, we'll learn about Bojanitsa's feelings towards water, Rusalka, and singing as a prima donna.
Yeah.  Yeah.   In the
current state of the Yagrado, only Posiniisa is still performing on stage, blaming it on the water.
Yeah.
yes.   There's a
feeling I have here.   I suppose so
.  yes.   It would be great if
Johnny's could continue singing in the future, wouldn't it?  yes.   Please make a wish
.
Please, I beg you.
Oh, and if you complete this mission, you'll also receive the appearance of Mike from Bojani Tour as a reward, so please look forward to version
7.1.
yes.  The new version will also feature new enemies.   At the
foot of the snowy mountains of Oesu, the traveler will encounter the snow-covered knight of Ie.
[Music]
Yes.
Defeating this knight will reward you with materials to unlock the new character, Besna.
yes.  Oh, next I'll introduce the event plans.
Okay,
in the first half of version 7.1, there will be an event prayer featuring Besna and Gozinny-chan.
yes.
Yeah.   In the second
half, the appearance rate of Scar and Escoffy increases.  Travelers who have been waiting for this should definitely not miss it.
yes.
Now, we'd like to take a break, but before that, we actually have a secret guest joining us later.
Yeah.
yes.   We'll be
bringing you information about version events, anniversary celebrations, and the current fate of the stars, so please stay tuned!
[Music]
And now we'll hand the baton over to our guest and that's where we'll end.
So, what did you think of the
first half of the preview program with the three of you today?
[Laughs]
Yeah.   That was
kind of fun, wasn't it?  It was
interesting.  When I first saw Bozni before he appeared, I wondered what kind of vibe this was, and how I was going to get into it, but it was really fun.
[Laughs] It seems like they know what I'm up to
.  It was fun, it was really fun
.   There were
all sorts of roles like doctor and teacher [music]
[laughter] Did
everyone get it all in their heads? Semi-chan mainly played all the different roles.  thank you.
[Laughs] It was like
he was appearing and disappearing, so it was hard to tell if he had come out or not
.  [Laughs] I
realized today that I'm really focused when I'm creating things during regular recording sessions.
[Laughs] He's
quite a calm and composed character, isn't he?   I
agree.   She has a
personality that's the complete opposite of most people; she loves butts, and she's always going out to talk to people.
Yeah.  Yeah.  Cute.  The story of Snejina is quite serious, but the uncle and older brother are incredibly comforting.  I'm so happy.
[Crying] I was
really quite fuming, so there were a lot of scenes where I got angry, and while recording I was wondering if everyone would be able to relax.  Yeah.
Because everyone is just an illusion.  Because it's an illusion.
[Laughs] are
not true.  When Johnny's Tour members approach someone and strike up a conversation, it can soften the mood and make the conversation progress more smoothly.   It's really
cute to see the two of them, along with Bojaniza and Olette, talking together.
Everyone thinks they're the most responsible one, which is kinda cute.
[Laughs] I mean,
how did the three of us become friends?
[Music]
Ah, I'm really curious if it's okay to say "like hanging out together".
[Laughs]
Yeah.
hey.  Because everyone orders different kinds of food.
yes.  We have different tastes and different personalities.
Yeah.
yes.  So, I hope that aspect will be explored further in the future.   I'm looking forward to it
.
yes.
yes.  So, until next time,
everyone.
thank you very much.
thank you very much.  see you.  I did.
Okay, so let's
enjoy version 7.1 together and look forward to it [music].
Now, let's move on to the second exchange.
After the break, please enjoy the preview program for the original version 7.1
.
[Music]
Welcome back, thanks to several voice actors for bringing you automated information.
Ladies and gentlemen, I am a great old friend of mine.   After a
long time on the road to the master, we will soon welcome the native six weeks, and while we are here, we will be studying together as a representative group, and congratulations to all the travelers who will be happy for six weeks.
1st edition of our activities and 1st anniversary.   I'm a
tourist, I'm a mission designer, and I'm happy for six weeks.
I am a master of design, a turning point in my career, and a happy six-year-old traveler.
[Music] A
new friend of mine, a new friend, a birthday celebration of the year, I listened to Li Yue's first dragon section, and I was in Zhang Dengsetsai, seven minutes ago.
[Music] I'm
confused, I'm not sure what to do, and I'm preparing for this.
哦, it was five years ago
2.1 When the version
of the original version was released, at that time, Li Yue's return to the school was completed, and the individual version was full of enthusiasm.
I can remember that I can't remember the story of the king of Guo.   Every time
I return to the Lord's Moon Festival, Li Yue Ren's statue is sitting on the floor, and the images are taken by Shu Bei.
哎、Looking at you, I understand that the bamboo festival is coming back.   What is the
connection between the master of the path, the master of the path, the master of the moon, and the immortal?
哈哈, it is impossible to defeat me, it is natural that I am the White Horse Immortal White, the confusion, the four editions of the month of the month, the 4th edition of the sea, and the origin of the month's festival, and the connection between the origin of the Hakuba Immortal and the Lord of the Month.
This is, and the history of the last month, written by the main month, has been slightly changed.  2.1 During
the story of the main month of the edition, I understand the story of the demon god of fire making.
[Music]
After the festival, the main moon set was gradually developed, and the tradition of the world's best arts was introduced.
I now return to the boiled black oven with a serious impression, and it is a great experience, and I have no idea how many people have boiled the boiled water.  Yes, five people forgot small rice cakes.
I listen to the teacher in Li Yue's house, but it is possible that other tastes and reviews are not the same.  In fact, it is a gastronomy that has been around for many years.
[music]  When I
saw the confession, the first prize of a year of peace and friendship was the customs of my heart, and the money was given to me.  During the holidays, other people are busy enough, so that the peasants can have peace of mind.
[Music] During
my impression, I arrived at 5.3 million seas to bring back the blessings of the eight flags.
Watching other people in that year, Yakki Senna-like, I left my head and had my own strength.
[Music]
Li Yuechuan's dissemination has come and gone as the century progresses.
In this year's main month, it appears on the top of the table.
[Music]
Yes, the traveler has no problem.
[music]  In the middle of the story
, I have one person who has a license, I have written a song written by a sister of the tribe who listens to the song, and I have completed the production of other crafts.  Spiritual evil energy, in the midst of the song, evil pursuit, individual play method, traveler demand manager, 盡possible collection along the way, some are scattered blood energy.  When I feel the rise and return, I have fully matured, and the good image is the divine treasure of the law, and I look at the small rise of the human ability, and the lack of people.
[music]  This is correct
, this is the first song designed by Kofuji, the evasion of the peasants, and the fact that there is one more than that, the background story of how the amount of spiritual power of the human being was improved, the method of play, listening to music, etc.  The truth is that the master of the temple is the master of the temple, and while we are in the midst of compiling the necessary clothing, there is a demand for travelers within a certain period of time, and it is possible that we may create more enemies and injure more people.
[Music]
哦, the precepts will be delivered, the truth will not be obtained, and the rebirth will be completed.
However, the number of formalities is unreturnable, the manned production is a kind of sophisticated mechanism, and the significant form of the passage of the master's function is a demonic scene.  During the challenge, the traveler can pass through the route, and the enemy can defeat the enemy.  During the course of the battle, the spiritual power that I gained during the battle was even stronger.   When I came to
listen to it, I felt the excitement of the next main clause.   This is the story of an
interesting traveler who has come to visit us, except for the first time I read a story about the Lord's Moon Festival.
[Music]
It's true that the main month's net room is a network room, and I'm not going to be able to do it.   The
story is similar to this, but I understand that Zhong Li and Shiyadu did not understand the incident, so the demand for the traveler and the old friend's search for crude oil.   I
understand that there are no other cities, there are many stories behind the scenes, and the traveler is the main business of the traveler.
[Music]
In addition to this, there are various activities such as passing, playing, and other interesting activities, as well as other activities for travelers, such as receiving or receiving gemstones.
[Music] Hiroyoshi
Towashi, East's children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children, children being all having a chance to play beings to be entertained and snowfall being played in one place, a genius sugar beet, a level of success, and a story of investment snowballs and defeats.
During the course of the trip, the tourists encountered various kinds of monsters, defeated others, gained integral abilities, gained talent during the period, gained talent from the ground, added genius sugar and oil, helped others to return to power, defeated more enemies, and won more reputations.
[Music]
The next time a traveler can return, he or she will have a special night's test, and a winning ticket for exploration.
誒，怎麼麼亚对于对一下，嗯，并且轻轻协卷專家用加热等人正步骤的一个实验测斗板simulated battle, the test group concludes a single ability to estimate the probability of winning model.  Shared by Hajime Honji
[Music]
[Music] 16
squads participate, a small squad competes in a number of battles that progress within a certain period of time, an average final victory, a winning technique in the midst of tourist demand, and a prediction that the squad competes every time.
[Music]
Now, I'm looking forward to the next visit to the capital, where I'll be able to see monsters and enemies from all over the place, and other people who will feel the pain of the meeting.
As a traveler, we need to predict the level of prediction, and also record the details of the team's lineup, appearance position, complete statistical support rate, etc., comprehensive analysis and selection.
[Music]
Miwa's great master only needs to vote and can get a vote.   I
have a certain intention, I have predicted that I can return after uniting, I can directly watch the battle between the troops, I will return the tower, I will explain the actual situation of the current situation, I will not repeat the decision, I will confirm that I got it, and I will vote first.
[Music]
This love story, the final battle in the middle of nowhere, a complete new challenge observation, a complete challenge return organic meeting acquisition, a complete new head statue outside the frame.
It is possible to acquire a number of people who have won a lot of money, and who have won a lot of work.   The
seven winning summons were also renewed, and the entire new horn color card was updated, and the moon crystal anti-reduction was also added to the seven-body summoning.
[Music]
Confusion, this outside Abeta, sugar return, Raizawa and the addition of a completely new magical natural gift effect, and the elimination of the combination of playability and the first step of the promotion.   I'm impressed by
the individual edition's activities, which are enough to cover the topic, and the most important things about the landlord.
[Music]
I'm here to tell the story of Fuku no Goharashin's arrival on my 6th birthday.
Naturally, it is necessary to stay in the country for the next week, the traveler will be able to pass through the mail, and the commemorative road activities will be carried out, and it will be possible to receive the certificate, pay attention to it, support ten pieces, and receive 1,600 yuan of various gifts.
[Music]
During the 7.1 edition, a traveler was able to return to the train, and a small train was opened, and the train commander was on the train.
[Music] It's
not just a cute commercial gold car coach, a traveler can pass the mail or get a special prop, the train is difficult to get, and the train after the train is a little interesting interaction.
Of course,
after updating the 7.1 version, the number of players in the game will be increased, and the number of self-selected players will be renewed, and the travelers will be able to participate in the same program this year.
[Music]
Now the landlord's preparation is enough, and the next step is definitely very cute.
[Music] I do
n't know if the traveler can return, I don't know if the preparations are overdue, and I'm surprised that the preparations are overdue.  Thank you
for your support and companionship for the global traveler who has been here for six years, and this year we have prepared a special gift for the return of our items.
[Music] A
limited number of five star horns sent outside the frame of the meeting.
In July, the 100th edition book period, Genshin Sho's promotion limited five star kakuiro self-selection activities, and the prelude to the adventure of the troupe.
[Music] The
7.1 mission is a famous anthem for the completion of the 7.1 mission by the predecessor, limited to 6th rank and above, five star horns, optional participation in the 1st rank, self-ranking, ordinary and returnable, extra-ordinary acquisition, and training materials for the 6th rank.
[Music]
[Music] Is the
original long-term five-star training material available?
However, it is not possible to carry out individual activities this year, in the future, every week in the future, we will be limited to the promotion of the city council, and the self-selected activities will be limited to five stars.
[Music] In
the midst of the activities of the future great family, we will be happy to hear from you.
[Music]
This year is the 6th anniversary of Genshin.
Tokimitsu, who has been traveling with Nowa for the past six years, has been a very lucky incident.
[Music]
We would like to express our sincere thanks to all the travelers who have sent us a special occasion.
[Music] I
also hope for a long time to come.
[Music]
Thank you very much for your welfare and blessings.   When I
woke up, it was my 6th year to participate in the battle, and every time I came back to the capital, I felt grateful for the meeting, and every year I was in the city, I had a completely new content.
[Music]
Half a year before the statue was created, the story of Japan's eastern and post-Bakumoku period was revealed, and at that time the items had reached a certain level.
At the end of July 7, 2015, the children's experience was completed, and the special delivery method of Higashi Higashi, the design method, the return model's experience, etc.
[Music]
One year ago, the Sky Song version was launched, and the landlord was able to achieve the same feeling of continuity.
[Music] If you understand the
concept of the future, you should be able to enjoy it, accept it, and believe in it.
[Music]
[Music] When
I came back to see it, Gozai Peiyin Roshi was introduced to the introduction of the horn color, and the special performance form of Uya Nisana, the item group was also announced earlier.
[Music]
[Music]  This is exactly what happened
before I arrived, and when I arrived at the landlord's body, I was able to see the landlord's face.  In the midst of being cautious, I hope that the future traveler will come and have a better experience, and hope that the traveler will not be able to see the light of the future.
[Music]
[Music] It's a
forward-looking dynamic, and it's always a forward-looking dynamic.
[Music]
Something new,
something exciting,
something out of
imagination.   The original
god of creation that I have come to believe that continues to exist.   If
you are able to do so, you will be able to put together a single point, of course, I will return to the same place as the original God item group, and if you have the best hope, you will be able to reach the world without interruption, and the possibility of further additions to the world, and the joy of creating more creators.
[Music] There are
many possibilities, great power, no payoff, many transparent exposure, one point?   Gosai Gaya
's creative philosophy was brought to him, and his writings were based on a certain number of phrases.
[Music] I have been here for a
long time, and I have had some problems with the landlord, but I have not yet met the original frame, and this is a completely new development.
[Music]
As soon as possible, the feelings and emotions of the landlord are open to the public, and the landlord is still accompanied by a direct companion, and the landlord is able to reach his full potential and has an unparalleled sense of kindness.  A small master's practice has always brought about an unexpected change in the East and West, and a completely uneven charm.
Well, I'm really looking forward to hearing it again.
More information about Chisaki, who returned after the story.
[Music]
Ah
[Singing voice]
[Music]
Ah [Music] [Singing voice]
.  [Singing voice]
Ah
.
[Music]
Oyako, I am a technology engineer.   Oyako
, I am a systematic strategy.
Zaifuka new gray.   A
one-year milestone in the development of the thousand star game law.   The
7.1 edition of the 7.1 edition of ``The Great Family Comes Next'' contains an updated and vivid interior.
[Music] A
new version of the book featuring a completely new series of costumes.   It's easy to
understand what's going on.
[Music]
O
[Music] The
main theme of the show, the costumes, and the one-sided style.
I have received a request for a special contract from the reporter, so I have been able to proceed with the design, and I have been connected to the site.
You like en
you like beans.   The new version of the
new version of this book is a little designed by Kyoichi.
Good soil beans.   The
new edition of this book is a new thematic masterpiece for the new owner.
A small cool house in a large building, a busy place in a small cool house, a busy place in the middle of a busy day.
[Music] A
special expression of the appearance after the continuation of the toy family friend.   A
style of costume that is based on the original idea of ​​Kazuto Watanabe.
Autumn day, art student Keika Watsuki Ryo's theme, design of the costume, antique color and antique costume, parallel wave, cloud view, one item of spirit, production completed and special effects.
[Music] The
new version of the book has been updated with a series of distinctive costumes, and in addition, the new version has been updated with a series of special costumes.
Etc., etc., in the direct distribution of the movie, is it similar to the past when you have a strange story?
After updating the current 7.1 edition, a strange autumn mask with a dramatic flavor was displayed as a gift to my friends and friends.   When did
Helen return to the scene? Due to some unexpected circumstances, there was no influence on the scene, and the scene progressed quickly, one step after another.   We
are currently preparing to hold a special exhibition in the Thousand Stars period to celebrate the success of the event.
Special information about the activities of the members of the group.   Currently
in the 7.1 edition, Shichishinzaki Masaharu's next opening is directed to the non-commercial donation activities, possession purchase order is provided by hand, the first purchase is possible non-amount acquisition items Eiwa Shengkai.
At the same time, the second edition of the book was sent by mail, and at the same time, various costumes were worn in the shopping center, and Chisaki returned to the store.
[Music] A
long-term plan for presenting materials and performing arts activities.
[Music]
Updated contents of the continuation of the toy house.   In
this case, I hope that my friends and I will be able to get a permanent residence at the hospital.
[Music]
Beyond the self-playing method, the wisdom of that man is a thousand stars and a variety of things.
At the time of the Tadashi meeting, I will participate in the selection activities of my friends and friends.
[Music]
Selected landlord's most representative sexual household items.
Passing the goal of completing the meeting, accumulating the popularity of the meeting, touring the friends of friends, including the guest's appearance, and promoting the promotion of multiple prizes.
After certain conditions have been met, the game's friends will be allowed to proceed with the vote.
After the activity was concluded, the total number of votes, its weight and other multiple factors, and the birth and success of the successive events were observed for 20 years.
In addition to this, we are looking forward to the release of the new edition of the special webpage of the ``Seishin no Yakusaki Sakidama Creation Daisaiyo Kishin Shengkai'' and the new edition of the book.
[Music] The
second version of the moon has now been published, and the entire world has exceeded 90,000 names, and the total number of works has exceeded 12,000.
I am very happy to see that I have made a series of changes, but I have also continued to develop new editing abilities.   The
latest version of the book, edited by the editor, has been updated.
In the process of editing the existing surface of the neck, the space of the first class can be placed at the end of the book
.
[Music]
Freedom to develop one's own imagination, more creativity and unexpected content.
In addition to the new edition of this book, we have collaborated with the model function, and the family has been able to request multiple copies of the first edition, edited and preserved, and are the director of each exhibition.
[Music]
Simultaneously Yuichi criticizes the scene material entering the Sensei period.
In the future, we will continue to provide more multi-dimensional editing ability, comprehensive super-line human number expansion, and support different parts of alternating and alternating play functions since the design play method.   In
this case, the creation of ecological support, the construction and the continuation of the company's continuous development, and the policy of new innovations and new business developers to plan for the continuation of the project, so that the same growth step is differentiating the support policy.
[Music]
In addition to the distribution of internal flow, the real content of the game player and the progress of the game's entertainment are improved, and the content of the game is more efficient and faster.
Thank you for the support of Tomoya Tomoyuki and Flag, Tomoyoshi and Senboshizaki.
[Music] A new
creation that surprises me.
Dear Friends, Rewatched the next episode.
The contents of the next thousand hearts are full, and the truth is that the earth is full of darkness.
Yes, I have been infected by others.   When the
arrival comes, the theme song for the 6th year of Genshin will be released soon, and everyone looking forward to it will be looking forward to it.
[Music]
Arrival.  As the next frontal turning point approaches, the tail is heard.   I have
heard the latest information, and I have very high expectations for the upcoming event, which will change the story of the current meeting.
[Music]
Hope is in the future, a colorful itinerary in the middle of the edition, with all the masters participating.   The
secrets of my performance and my secrets are slowly unfolding in front of my face.
[Music] I am a master of
writing about the world's stories and stories.
[Music]
I was looking forward to the world's best stories from Hongdae, and at the same time, I was deeply moved by the truth.
When I returned to the capital, I was in Monde during the first study flight, and I was a wealthy traveler.
[Music]
[Music] Of
course, while I was on the road, I lost track of my strength, and the time when I returned home was very enjoyable.
[Music]
This is a special itinerary for the owner and the traveler for six years of joint growth.
[Music] The
truth is the passion of a great master, the true life force of the original god.
[Music]
Every time I look at a traveler's new land, I look at a new color of joy, I look at a society's original source of brilliant creations, and I'm sure that I'll add new things to the city.
[Music] As a matter of fact
, I also feel that I am responsible for this issue, and that I am responsible for this, and that I have continued to create and create a future that is astounding.   The
6th year is a milestone, and it is also a brilliant period.
[Music] This is a
more colorful story of how the traveler continues to accompany the original deity, and how he feels when he starts and leaves.
[Music]
Thank you again for the first place, a companion god has arrived, a traveler in heaven, Nara six weeks of pleasure, and I
September 23rd new edition book review.
[Music]
Pleasant [Music]